

Ghaith Al-Refaee

Software developer

i have 25 years old, I am a professional back-end developer with experience in managing and resolving technical issues related to computers and networks. I specialize in programming, application development, and website development, delivering efficient and scalable solutions.

- UAE, Dubai, Abu Dhabi
- github.com/ghith-refae

+971523045778

SKILLS

in linkedin.com/in/Ghaith Al-Refae

Adobe Xd

instagram.com/Ghaith Rifai

Flutter

Adobe After effects

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer Remote Task System

01/2023 - 12/2024

Application development, and website development, delivering efficient and scalable solutions.

Help desk ISP Inet

01/2021 - 07/2021 Damascus-Syria

One of the leading Internet Service Providers in Syria.

Achievements/Tasks

Technical support

System Developer **IZONE Solutions**

01/2020 - 08/2020

is an IT outsourcing company delivers customer-service. IZONE Technology Response Team is a real partner in your business technology.

ACHIEVEMENTS

IZONE SOLUUION

Successfully repaired and optimized the surveillance camera system at Al-Sham Private University, ensuring enhanced security and seamless operation across the campus

Photoshop

android studio

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in communications technology

Syrian virtual university

01/2019 - Present

Courses

 I have 1classes remaining to complete my degree. with the option to skip attendance due to my experience.

Technical Institute for Software engineering.

Damascus University

01/2019 - 01/2022

LANGUAGES

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency